flavorpill.com 2014-06-18

# Flavorpill

## Privacy Policy

_Last updated: July 10, 2012_

### About Flavorpill:

Welcome to Flavorpill, a product of Flavorpill Productions LLC (“Flavorpill”). Flavorpill enables people all over the world to plan, promote, and share any event, and to converse about that event with a community of culturally connected people.

We do this through our websites and domains, the services available on or through our websites and domains or otherwise provided by us, and the software available on or through our websites and domains or otherwise provided by us (collectively, the "Services").

### Our Policy:

This Privacy Policy sets forth our policy with respect to information, including personally identifiable information ("Personal Data"), that is collected from users of and/or visitors to the Services (including through those users' and visitors' agents) ("you" or "your"), including (i) registered users who input event information ("Creators"), and (ii) non-Creator users or visitors to the Services ("other non-Creators").

We take the privacy of your Personal Data and other information seriously. Because of that, we have created this Privacy Policy. Please read this Privacy Policy as it includes important information regarding your Personal Data and other information.

If you have any questions or concerns, please do not hesitate to contact us by using the following link: [info@flavorpill.com](mailto:info@flavorpill.com)

### CONSENT:

**By using the Services or allowing someone to use the Services on your behalf, you are consenting to our collection, use, disclosure, transfer and storage in accordance with this Privacy Policy of any Personal Data or other information received by us as a result of such use.**

### Information We Collect:

When you interact with us through the Services, we may collect Personal Data and other information from you, as further described below:

  1. #### Personal Data:

We collect Personal Data from you when you voluntarily provide such information to the Services (including event pages within the Services). The Personal Data we may collect includes without limitation your name, address, email address and other personally identifiable information.

**Privacy Policy Links:** We make an effort to provide a link to this Privacy Policy in the footer of every page on our websites, including those pages on which Personal Data is collected, and to make it available in all of our software. 

  2. #### Non-Personal Data:

**Non-Identifiable Data:** When you interact with the Services, we collect certain personally non-identifiable information ("Non-Personal Data"). The Non-Personal Data we collect includes without limitation Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, Internet browser type, other characteristics of your device and software, domain names of your Internet Service Provider, your approximate geographic location, a record of your usage of the Services, the time of your usage and aggregated Personal Data that cannot be used to specifically identify you. Such information, which is collected passively using various technologies, cannot, in and of itself, be used to specifically identify you. We also collect Non-Personal Data (including, without limitation, of the type set forth above) from third parties. The information we collect from third parties may be combined with the information we collect. 

**Cookies and Other Session Identifiers:** In operating the Services, we use a technology called "cookies." A cookie is a piece of information that is placed on your browser when you access the Services. Our cookies help provide additional functionality to the Services and help us analyze Service usage more accurately. For instance, our Services may set a cookie on your browser that allows you to access the Services without needing to remember and then enter a password more than once during a visit. These cookies may be used to tailor content (including advertising) you see on the Services as well as other Internet sites that you may visit in the future. Cookies may be session cookies (i.e., last only for one browser session) or persistent cookies (i.e., continue in your browser until they are deleted or expire). Through your web browser's option settings you may be able (i) to receive notifications when you are receiving new cookies, (ii) to disable cookies or (iii) to delete cookies. Please refer to your web browser's help section for information on how to do this. We recommend that you leave cookies turned on because they allow you to take advantage of some of the features of the Services. In addition to the types of cookies described above, we use local shared objects, also known as "Flash cookies," and HTML 5 Local Storage for various purposes, including for fraud prevention and to display content (both on and off the Services) based upon what you view on the Services. Local shared objects and HTML 5 Local Storage are different from cookies described above. Cookie management tools provided by your browser may not remove local shared objects or HTML 5 Local Storage. 

**Aggregated Personal Data:** In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Services, we often conduct research on our customer demographics, interests and behavior based on Personal Data and other information that we have collected. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis and this aggregate information does not identify you personally and therefore is considered and treated as Non-Personal Data under this Privacy Policy. 

### Our Use of Information That We Collect:

  1. #### Personal Data:

We use the Personal Data we collect in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. We may use the Personal Data as follows:

    * **Specific Reason:** If you provide Personal Data for a certain reason, we may use the Personal Data in connection with the reason for which it was provided. For instance, if you contact us by e-mail, we will use the Personal Data you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem and will respond to the email address from which the contact came. 

    * **Internal Business Purposes:** We may use your Personal Data for internal business purposes including without limitation to help us improve the content and functionality of the Services, to better understand our users, to improve the Services, to protect against, identify or address wrongdoing, to enforce our Terms of Service, to manage your account and provide you with customer service, and to generally manage the Services and our business. 

    * **Marketing:** We may use your Personal Data to contact you in the future for our marketing and advertising purposes, including without limitation to inform you about services or events we believe might be of interest to you, to develop promotional or marketing materials and provide those materials to you, and to display content and advertising on or off the Services that we believe might be of relevance to you. In particular, Creators should note that we may use information we receive or collect regarding Buyers (including without limitation via an Creator’'s event registration page) in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy, including in the manner set forth above. 

If we intend to use any Personal Data in any manner that is not consistent with this Privacy Policy, you will be informed of such anticipated use prior to or at the time at which the Personal Data is collected or we will obtain your consent subsequent to such collection but prior to such use.

  2. #### Non-Personal Data:

Because Non-Personal Data cannot be used to personally identify you, we may use such information for any lawful purpose.

### Our Disclosure of Information That We Collect:

  1. #### Personal Data:

We are not in the business of selling your Personal Data. We consider this information to be a vital part of our relationship with you. Therefore, we will not sell your Personal Data to third parties, including third party advertisers. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may disclose, transfer or share your Personal Data with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below:

**Business Transfers:** As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, Personal Data may be part of the transferred assets. You acknowledge and agree that any successor to or acquiror of Flavorpill(or its assets) will continue to have the right to use your Personal Data and other information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

**Subsidiaries and Affiliates:** We may also share your Personal Data with our subsidiaries and/or affiliates for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy. Our subsidiaries and affiliates will be bound to maintain that Personal Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties:** We, like many businesses, sometimes engage other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples of such functions include mailing information, ticket fulfillment, fraud prevention, maintaining databases and processing payments. When we engage another company to perform such functions, we may provide them with information, including Personal Data, in connection with their performance of such functions. 

**Facebook and Other Third Party Connections:** You can connect your Flavorpill account to your accounts on third party services like Facebook, in which case we may collect, use, disclose, transfer and store information relating to your account with such third party services in accordance with this Privacy Policy. For example, if you connect with Facebook, we store your Facebook id, first name, last name, email, location, friends list and profile picture and use them to connect with your Facebook account to provide certain functionality on the Services, like recommending events that your Facebook friends are interested in and sharing the events you are interested in with certain groups of people like your Facebook friends. 

**Legal Requirements:** We may disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law (including, without limitation responding to a subpoena or request from law enforcement, court or government agency) or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary (i) to comply with a legal obligation, (ii) to protect or defend our rights, interests or property or that of third parties, (iii) to prevent, investigate, or identify possible wrongdoing in connection with the Services, (iv) to act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Services or the public, or (v) to protect against legal liability. 

  2. #### Non-Personal Data:

Because Non-Personal Data cannot be used to personally identify you, we may disclose, transfer or share Non-Personal Data for any lawful purpose.

### Your Choices:

You have several choices available when it comes to your Personal Data:

**Limit the Personal Data You Provide:** You can use the Services while limiting the Personal Data you provide. If you choose to limit the Personal Data you provide, you may not be able to use certain functionality of the Services. 

**Opt Out:** You can "opt out" of receiving Flavorpill emails by emails by logging in, selecting "Settings" from the user dropdown menu, and unchecking the options in question. You may modify your choices at any time in your Gal account. In the event you receive an email related to an event, you will be able to "opt out" of receiving those communications as well. 

#### Exclusions:

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Data collected by us other than Personal Data collected through the Services. This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to us or another user or visitor through the Services or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Services, such as discussion boards, any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, claim or demand letters, Digital Millennium Copyright Act notices, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, "Unsolicited Information"). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and we shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, distribute and exploit such Unsolicited Information without limitation or attribution.

#### Children:

We do not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any Personal Data through the Services. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children's Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Data through the Services without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Data to us through the Services, please [contact us](mailto:privacy@flavorpill.com) and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases. 

#### Links to Other Web Sites:

This Privacy Policy applies only to the Services. The Services may contain links to other websites not operated or controlled by us (the "Third Party Sites"). The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to the Third Party Sites. The links from the Services do not imply that we endorse or have reviewed the Third Party Sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies.

#### Storage and Security:

We may store Personal Data itself or such information may be included in databases owned and maintained by our affiliates, agents or service providers. We take what we believe to be reasonable steps to protect the Personal Data provided via the Services from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, inadvertent disclosure, alteration, and destruction. However, no Internet or e-mail transmission is ever fully secure or error free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from the Services may not be secure. Therefore, you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail. Please keep this in mind when disclosing any Personal Data via the Internet.

#### International Privacy Laws:

If you are visiting our website or using one of our software applications from outside the United States, please be aware that you are sending information (including Personal Data) to the United States where our servers are located. We will hold and process your Personal Data and Non-Personal Data in accordance with privacy laws in the United States and this Privacy Policy. Please note that privacy laws in the United States may not be the same as, and in some cases may be less protective than, the privacy laws in your country.

#### Other Terms and Conditions:

Your access to and use of the Services is subject to the Terms of Service.

#### Changes to This Privacy Policy:

The Services and our business may change from time to time. As a result, at times it may be necessary for us to make changes to this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time by posting a new version of this Privacy Policy on our websites. Please review this policy periodically, and especially before you provide any Personal Data. This Privacy Policy was last updated on the date indicated above. Your continued use of the Services after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.

#### Access to Information:

Creators, Consumers and other users may access and update their Personal Data being stored by us by logging in and visiting the Edit Profile page, and may also contact us directly at the address specified below with respect to Personal Data that is not accessible through the Edit Profile page.

#### Retention and Deletion:

We may retain your Personal Data as long as you continue to use the Services. You may close your account by contacting us. However, we may retain Personal Data and Non-Personal Data for an additional period as is permitted or required under applicable laws. Even if we delete your Personal Data it may persist on backup or archival media and other information systems.

#### Contacting Flavorpill:

Please also feel free to [contact us](mailto:info@flavorpill.com) if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our information practices. 

#### Dispute Resolution:

If you have a complaint about Flavorpill's privacy practices you should write to us at Flavorpill Productions, LLC., Attn: Privacy Officer, 594 Broadway, Suite 1212, New York, NY 10012, USA, or by email to [privacy@flavorpill.com](mailto:privacy@flavorpill.com) We will take reasonable steps to work with you to attempt to resolve your complaint.
